Guide to the Northern Pacific Railway Company Records 1870-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Engineering Department, 1870-1968; Subgroup 1; 165.25 linear feet and 14 oversize volumes
  - Photographs, 1882-1959; Series XXII; 2.0 linear feet and 1 oversize box
    - Tracklaying machine, undated; 128(XXII):336 or 95-427 (Box 395)
    - Foley Brothers tracklaying machine, undated; 128(XXII):337 or 95-428 (Box 395)
    - Foley Brothers tracklaying machine, undated; 128(XXII):338 or 95-429 (Box 395)
    - Tracklaying machine, undated; 128(XXII):339 or 95-430 (Box 395)
    - Foley Brothers tracklaying machine (negative only), undated; 128(XXII):340 or 95-431 (Box 395)
    - Driving Bridge no. 1, 1927-08-01; 128(XXII):341 or 95-432 (Box 395)
    - Bridge no. 1, 1927-08-19; 128(XXII):342 or 95-433 (Box 395)
    - Ice jam in front of Bridge 2, station 182 (negative only), 1928-01-11; 128(XXII):343 or 95-434 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 2, station 182, 1928-01-11; 128(XXII):344 or 95-435 (Box 395)
    - Ice jam at Bridge 2, station 182, 1928-01-11; 128(XXII):345 or 95-436 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 2, station 182, 1928-01-11; 128(XXII):346 or 95-437 (Box 395)
    - Bridge no. 2, 1928-01-12; 128(XXII):347 or 95-438 (Box 395)
    - Breaking up ice in front of bridge no. 2 (negative only), 1928-01-02; 128(XXII):348 or 95-439 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 4-3, Station 581, 1927-10-12; 128(XXII):349 or 95-440 (Box 395)
    - Bridge opening no. 5, station 682 (negative only), 1927-08-08; 128(XXII):350 or 95-441 (Box 395)
    - Driver at bridge no. 16, station 1050, 1927-10-12; 128(XXII):351 or 95-442 (Box 395)
    - Laying track over bridge at station 1330 (negative only), 1928-10-27; 128(XXII):352 or 95-443 (Box 395)
    - Driving Bridge no. 1, 1927-08-11; 128(XXII):353 or 95-444 (Box 395)
    - Bridge no. 22 at station 1670, 1928-01-16; 128(XXII):354 or 95-445 (Box 395)
    - Bridge no. 22, station 1670, 1928-03-22; 128(XXII):355 or 95-446 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 24, station 1820, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):356 or 95-447 (Box 395)
    - Work at bridge no.24, station 1820, 1928-03-16; 128(XXII):357 or 95-448 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 25, station 1900, undated; 128(XXII):358 or 95-449 (Box 395)
    - Bridge 25, station 1900, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):359 or 95-450 (Box 395)
    - Driving bridge no. 36, undated; 128(XXII):360 or 95-451 (Box 395)
    - Settlement at station 205, 1928-01-20; 128(XXII):361 or 95-452 (Box 395)
    - Settlement at Station 205, 1928-01-01; 128(XXII):362 or 95-453 (Box 395)
    - Summit camp, 1927-08-18; 128(XXII):363 or 95-454 (Box 395)
    - Summit cut looking east, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):364 or 95-455 (Box 395)
    - Shovel in summit cut, looking west, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):365 or 95-456 (Box 395)
    - Summit cut looking east, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):366 or 95-457 (Box 395)
    - Mantry Peterson’s camp at Divide, 1928-01-23; 128(XXII):367 or 95-458 (Box 395)
    - Mantry Peterson’s working in summit cut (negative only), 1928-02-03; 128(XXII):368 or 95-459 (Box 395)
    - Lindsay station grounds from depot site, Montana, 1927-10-12; 128(XXII):369 or 95-460 (Box 395)
    - Lindsay station grounds looking west from highway at station 1174, Montana, 1928-10-27; 128(XXII):370 or 95-461 (Box 395)
    - Lindsay station grounds looking west from station 1174, Montana, 1928-10-27; 128(XXII):371 or 95-462 (Box 395)
    - Midland Lumber Company Yard at Lindsay, Montana, 1927-11-30; 128(XXII):372 or 95-463 (Box 395)
    - Elevators at Lindsay, Montana, 1927-11-30; 128(XXII):373 or 95-464 (Box 395)
    - Elevators at Lindsay, Montana, 1928-01-10; 128(XXII):374 or 95-465 (Box 395)
    - Midland Lumber Company Yard at Lindsay, Montana (negative only), 1928-01-10; 128(XXII):375 or 95-466 (Box 395)
    - Lindsay, looking east from station 1200, Montana (negative only), 1928-01-16; 128(XXII):376 or 95-467 (Box 395)
    - Camp buildings at Lindsay, Montana, 1928-01-16; 128(XXII):377 or 95-468 (Box 395)
    - Company well drilling outfit at Lindsay, Montana, 1928-01-16; 128(XXII):378 or 95-469 (Box 395)
    - Temporary stock yards at Lindsay, Montana (negative only), 1928-01-16; 128(XXII):379 or 95-470 (Box 395)
    - Section house at Intake, 1928-11-23; 128(XXII):380 or 95-471 (Box 395)
    - Depot at Intake, 1928-11-23; 128(XXII):381 or 95-472 (Box 395)
    - Section house at Intake, 1927-11-29; 128(XXII):382 or 95-473 (Box 395)
    - Headquarters residency #4, Circle, Montana, undated; 128(XXII):383 or 95-474 (Box 395)
    - Ice lodged on west bank of Yellowstone River at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01; 128(XXII):384 or 95-475 (Box 395)
    - Flooding of river flats at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):385 or 95-476 (Box 395)
    - Flood across river bottoms from Station 3 (negative only), 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):386 or 95-477 (Box 395)
    - Flooding of river flats at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):387 or 95-478 (Box 395)
    - Looking west from highway bridge at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):388 or 95-479 (Box 395)
    - Flooding of river flats at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):389 or 95-480 (Box 395)
    - Flooding of river flats at Glendive from west approach to highway bridge, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):390 or 95-481 (Box 395)
    - Ice deposited on island following gorge at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):391 or 95-482 (Box 395)
    - Ice lodged on west bank of Yellowstone River by gorge at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01; 128(XXII):392 or 95-483 (Box 395)
    - Ice in river bank following gorge at Glendive, Montana. Top of ice 18' above river level, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):393 or 95-484 (Box 395)
    - Ice deposited on island following gorge at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):394 or 95-485 (Box 395)
    - Ice deposited in island following gorge at Glendive, Montana, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):395 or 95-486 (Box 395)
    - Ice pilled up on south bank of Yellowstone River at glacier, 18' above normal water level, 1928-01; 128(XXII):396 or 95-487 (Box 395)
    - Looking toward Glendive, Montana from Station 27, 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):397 or 95-488 (Box 395)
    - Looking toward Glendive, Montana from Station 27 (negative only), 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):398 or 95-489 (Box 395)
    - Looking toward Glendive, Montana from Station 27 (negative only), 1928-01-14; 128(XXII):399 or 95-490 (Box 395)
    - Bridge no. 2-1, Station 196, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):400 or 95-491 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 3, Station 396, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):401 or 95-492 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 4-4, Station 612, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):402 or 95-493 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 11, Station 850, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):403 or 95-494 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 14, Station 1000, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):404 or 95-495 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 15, Station 1030, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):405 or 95-496 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 37, Station 3014, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):406 or 95-497 (Box 396)
    - Bridge no. 37, Station 3014, 1928-11-20; 128(XXII):407 or 95-498 (Box 396)
    - Depot at Lindsay, Montana, 1928; 128(XXII):408 or 95-621 (Box 396)
    - Partial Index to Negatives, undated (Box 396)
    - Tunnels, Bridges, and Depots - Washington, Idaho, Montana, and North Dakota, undated (Box 396)
    - Bridges and Depots - Idaho, Montana, North Dakota, and Minnesota, undated (Box 396)
    - Railroad Construction Prints, Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1890 - 1893 (Box 397)
    - Bridges, Depots, Grain Elevators - Montana and North Dakota, 1934 and undated (Box 397)
    - Survey and Construction Prints, no location, undated (Box 397)
    - Tunnels - Washington, undated (Box 397)
    - Orofino Branch, Lewiston, Idaho, undated (Box 397)
    - Orofino Branch, Lewiston, Idaho, undated (Box 397)
    - Bridge construction - no location, undated (Box 397)
    - Railroad facilities - no location, undated (Box-folder OS1/1)
    - Railroad facilities - no location, undated (Box-folder OS1/2)
    - Bridge No. 9, Mississippi River, Minnesota, 1923 (Box-folder OS1/3)
    - Industrial Site, Billings, Montana, undated (Box-folder OS1/4)
    - Railroad Construction - no location, undated (Box-folder OS1/5)
    - Bridge and Depot Construction Photographs - Various locations in Washington, Idaho, Montana, and North Dakota, undated (Box-volume OS1/617)
    - Power Plant, Bridge and Depot Construction Photographs - Various locations in Washington, Idaho, Montana, North Dakota, and Minnesota, 1912 - 1930 and undated (Box-volume OS1/618)
- Branch Lines, Predecessors and Related Companies, 1881-1960; Subgroup 2; 60.75 linear feet and 18 oversize volumes
  This subgroup contains materials generated by employees of the branch, predecessor, and subsidiary lines associated with the Northern Pacific Railway Company. These materials were primarily generated by Engineering Department personnel and descriptive terminology is generally consistent with that of Subgroup 1. This subgroup consists of 37 series--most of which are essentially small fragments of the unit's original operations records. Materials include property acquistion correspondence, construction project records (correspondence, financial, and legal records), progress reports, line traffic summaries, and personnel documents.
  These materials provide significant primary resources for examining railroad corporate management structures, land ownership histories for properties associated with branch and subsidiary lines as well as regional and localized economic impacts created by railroad construction and repair. Information in this series is primarily presented through general correspondence, bound financial ledgers, compiled tracking reports and narrative summaries, blue print diagrams and maps, and day books maintained by unidentified railroad staff. Throughout this subgroup the phrase "Force Reports" in folder titles refers to reports filed by line engineers regarding actual and projected personnel hours (work force) for construction and repair projects.
  Historical and contextual information for some of the branch, predecessor, and related rail lines in this subgroup is very limited. Whenever possible, the scope and notes for each series identify the geographic location of the lines and dates for incoporation into the NPRR system.
  - Astoria and Columbia River Railroad Company, 1894-1898; Series XXIII; 1 folder
    The Astoria and Columbia River Railroad Company operated between Seaside and Goble, Oregon, from May 1898 to March 1911. This series contains one folder of general correspondence predating incorporation through July, 1898.
    - General Correspondence, 1894-03-08 - 1898-07-30 (Box-folder 267/8)
  - Bear Creek Western Railway Company, 1901-1910; Series XXIV; 1 folder
    This series contains one folder of general correspondence from Bear Creek Western Railway Company.
    - General Correspondence, 1901-12-20 - 1910-08-04 (Box-folder 267/9)
  - Camp Creek Railway Company, 1911-1912; Series XXV; 1.0 linear feet and 1 oversize volume
    The Camp Creek Railway Company operated between Manhattan and Anceny, Montana. It opened its line in 1912, and sold to the NPRR in June 1914. This series contains general correspondence, financial records, and maps pertaining to construction projects. These materials include payroll records, building designs, rights of way inquiries, supply requisitions, work force reports, and project estimates.
    - General Correspondence, Track Laying, 1911-08-11 - 1911-09-20 (Box-folder 268/1)
    - General Correspondence, Track Laying, 1911-09-21 - 1912-03-15 (Box-folder 268/2)
    - General Correspondence, Buildings, 1911-09-05 - 1911-11-20 (Box-folder 268/3)
    - General Correspondence, Buildings, 1911-11-21 - 1912-03-21 (Box-folder 268/4)
    - General Correspondence, Travel Passes, 1911-08-08 - 1912-05-03 (Box-folder 268/5)
    - General Correspondence, A.C. Terrell, 1911-09-14 - 1912-05-16 (Box-folder 268/6)
    - General Correspondence, Crossings with Gallatin Valley Electric Railroad, 1911-06-27 - 1911-09-20 (Box-folder 268/7)
    - General Correspondence, Engineer's Office, 1911-06-05 - 1912-04-10 (Box-folder 268/8)
    - General Correspondence, Alignment and Grades, 1911-06-13 - 1912-03-04 (Box-folder 268/9)
    - General Correspondence, Track, 1911-06-22 - 1912-03-04 (Box-folder 268/10)
    - General Correspondence, Rights of Way, 1911-06-17 - 1911-11-13 (Box-folder 268/11)
    - General Correspondence, Rights of Way, 1911-11-14 - 1912-05-12 (Box-folder 268/12)
    - General Correspondence, Fences, Telephone Lines, 1911-06-21 - 1912-05-15 (Box-folder 268/13)
    - General Correspondence, Payroll, 1911-07-13 - 1912-03-11 (Box-folder 268/14)
    - General Correspondence, Bridges, 1911-06-16 - 1912-05-15 (Box-folder 269/1)
    - General Correspondence, Material, 1911-06-24 - 1912-06-04 (Box-folder 269/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1911-06-12 - 1912-03-04 (Box-folder 269/3)
    - Financial Records, Shipments, 1911-06-21 - 1912-01-01 (Box-folder 269/4)
    - Construction Estimates, 1911-06 - 1911-07 (Box-folder 269/5)
    - Construction Estimates, 1911-08 - 1911-12 (Box-folder 269/6)
    - Requisitions, 1911-06-16 - 1912-02-17 (Box-folder 269/7)
    - Force Reports, 1911-07-08 - 1911-09-26 (Box-folder 269/8)
    - Force Reports, 1911-09-27 - 1911-10 (Box-folder 269/9)
    - Force Reports, 1911-11 - 1912-02-09 (Box-folder 269/10)
    - Maps and Drawings, 1911-06 - 1912-06 (Box-folder 269/11)
    - Car Book, 1911 (Volume 406)
  - Central Washington Railroad Company, 1888-1910; Series XXVI; 4.5 linear feet and 3 oversize volumes
    The Central Washington Railroad Company operated a line from Cheney to Coulee City, Washington. This series contains general construction correspondence and financial records, primarily detailing project proposals, rights of way inquiries, supply requisitions, progress reports, and work force reports.
    - General Correspondence, 1888-11-10 - 1889-04-15 (Box-folder 270/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-04-16 - 1889-05-25 (Box-folder 270/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-05-26 - 1889-06-25 (Box-folder 270/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-06 - 1889-07 (Box-folder 270/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-08-01 - 1889-08-25 (Box-folder 270/5)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-08-26 - 1889-09-27 (Box-folder 270/6)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-09-28 - 1889-10-20 (Box-folder 270/7)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-10-21 - 1889-11-10 (Box-folder 270/8)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-11-11 - 1889-11-28 (Box-folder 270/9)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-11-29 - 1889-12-14 (Box-folder 271/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1889-12-15 - 1890-01-09 (Box-folder 271/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-01-10 - 1890-01-31 (Box-folder 271/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-02-01 - 1890-02-17 (Box-folder 271/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-02-18 - 1890-03-08 (Box-folder 271/5)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-03-09 - 1890-04-09 (Box-folder 271/6)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-04-10 - 1890-05-10 (Box-folder 271/7)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-05-11 - 1890-06-30 (Box-folder 271/8)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-07-02 - 1890-07-31 (Box-folder 271/9)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-08-01 - 1890-08-31 (Box-folder 271/10)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-09-01 - 1890-10-09 (Box-folder 272/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-10-10 - 1890-11-30 (Box-folder 272/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1890-12-11 - 1891-04-10 (Box-folder 272/3)
    - General Correspondence, undated (Box-folder 272/4)
    - General Correspondence, Rights of Way, 1892-02 - 1901-08 (Box-folder 272/5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1909-04 - 1909-11 (Box-volume 273A/407)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1909-11 - 1910-01 (Box-volume 273A/408A)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1888-08 - 1889-05 (Box-volume 273A/408B)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, C. A. Reardon, 1889-05 - 1889-10 (Box-volume 273B/408C)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. C. Patterson, 1889-06 - 1891-03 (Box-volume 273B/408D)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, C. A. Reardon, 1889-10 - 1890-03 (Box-volume 273B/408E)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, C. A. Reardon, 1890-03 - 1890-08 (Box-volume 273B/408F)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. C. Patterson, 1890-08 - 1891-04 (Box-volume 273C/408G)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Index to Letters Received, 1889 - 1890 (Box-volume 273C/408H)
    - Vouchers, 1888-10 - 1889-10 (Box-volume 273C/408I)
    - Index to Volume 408I, 1888-10 - 1889-10 (Box-volume 273C/408J)
    - Vouchers, 1889-06 - 1891-04 (Volume 408K)
    - Index to Volume 408K, 1889-06 - 1891-04 (Volume 408L)
    - Requisitions, Invoices, and Estimates, 1889 - 1890 (Box-volume 273D/408M)
    - Department Bills, 1890-03 - 1891-03 (Box-volume 273D/408N)
    - Construction Material Used, Davenport to Almira (Washington), 1889-07 - 1889-09 (Box-volume 273D/408O)
    - Construction Material Used, Davenport to Almira (Washington), 1889-09 - 1890-07 (Box-volume 273D/408P)
    - Requisition and Material Distribution, 1890 (Box-volume 273D/408Q)
    - Requisition and Material Distribution, 1890 (Box-volume 273D/408R)
    - Time Reports (Trainmen), 1888-11 - 1889-05 (Box-volume 273D/408S)
    - Time Reports, 1889 - 1890 (Box-volume 273E/408T)
    - Time Reports (Engineer Service), 1889-02 - 1889-07 (Box-volume 273E/408U)
    - Time Reports (Engineer Service), 1889-03 - 1890-07 (Box-volume 273E/408V)
    - Time Reports (Laborers), 1889-04 - 1889-06 (Box-volume 273E/408W)
    - Time Reports (Trainmen), 1889-05 - 1890-03 (Box-volume 273E/408X)
    - Time Reports (Trainmen), 1889-05 - 1890-07 (Box-volume 273E/408Y)
    - Time Reports (Trainmen), 1889-09 - 1890-08 (Box-volume 273F/408Z)
    - Time Reports (Trainmen), 1889-10 - 1889-12 (Box-volume 273F/409A)
    - Time Reports (Engineer Service), 1889-10 - 1890-12 (Box-volume 273F/409B)
    - Time Reports (Train and Engine Men), 1903-05 - 1903-09 (Box-volume 273F/409C)
    - Trainmen's Time and Distribution, 1888-12 - 1890-05 (Volume 409D)
    - Records of Rights of Way Deeds, 1888-10 - 1889-06 (Box-volume 273F/409E)
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company, 1900-1960; Series XXVII; 5.5 linear feet
    The Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad Company operated main lines from Chicago, IL, to St. Paul, Minnesota, and to St. Louis, MO, and Cody, Wyoming. The CBQRR operated as an affiliated line to the NPRR until 1970 when (with the NPRR) it became a part of the Burlington Northern Railroad Company. This series contains extensive sequences of general correspondence and blueprints from several spurs of the Wyoming Division within the railroad company such as those to Casper, Cody, Worland, Garland, Greybull, and Kane. Blueprints in this series are particularly strong resources for identifying rights of way and land ownership patterns for central and northern Wyoming.
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1900's (Box-folder 274/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1920 - 1924 (Box-folder 274/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1925-01 - 1925-06 (Box-folder 274/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1925-07 - 1925-12 (Box-folder 274/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1926-01 - 1926-06 (Box-folder 275/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1926-07 - 1926-12 (Box-folder 275/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1927 (Box-folder 275/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1928 (Box-folder 275/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1929-01 - 1929-06 (Box-folder 276/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1929-07 - 1929-12 (Box-folder 276/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1930-01 - 1930-06 (Box-folder 276/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1930-07 - 1930-12 (Box-folder 276/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1931 (Box-folder 276/5)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1932 - 1933 (Box-folder 276/6)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1934 - 1935 (Box-folder 276/7)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1936 (Box-folder 277/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1937 (Box-folder 277/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1938 - 1939 (Box-folder 277/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1940 (Box-folder 277/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1941 - 1942 (Box-folder 278/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1943 (Box-folder 278/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1944 - 1945 (Box-folder 278/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1946-01 - 1946-07 (Box-folder 278/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1946-08 - 1946-12 (Box-folder 278/5)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1947 (Box-folder 278/6)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1948 - 1949 (Box-folder 279/1)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 279/2)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 279/3)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 279/4)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1960's (Box-folder 279/5)
    - General Correspondence, Casper Division, 1930's (Box-folder 280/1)
    - General Correspondence, Garland Division, 1923 - 1948 (Box-folder 280/2)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1920 - 1925 (Box-folder 280/3)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1926 - 1927 (Box-folder 280/4)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1928 - 1929 (Box-folder 280/5)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1930's (Box-folder 280/6)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 281/1)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1950's (Box-folder 281/2)
    - General Correspondence, Greybull Division, 1924 - 1926 (Box-folder 281/3)
    - General Correspondence, Kane Divison, 1925 - 1947 (Box-folder 281/4)
    - General Correspondence, Kirby Division, 1930 - 1949 (Box-folder 281/5)
    - General Correspondence, 1920 - 1929 (Box-folder 282/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1930 - 1939 (Box-folder 282/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1940 - 1949 (Box-folder 282/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1920 - 1949 (Box-folder 282/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1920 - 1949 (Box-folder 282/5)
    - General Correspondence, 1920 - 1955 (Box-folder 282/6)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1930 - 1950 (Box-folder 283/1)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1910 - 1940 (Box-folder 283/2)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1920 - 1950 (Box-folder 283/3)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa1920 - 1940 (Box-folder 283/4)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1900 - 1940 (Box-folder 283/5)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1920 - 1950 (Box-folder 283/6)
    - Blueprints, Casper Division, circa 1940 - 1950 (Box-folder 283/7)
    - Blueprints, Cody Division, circa 1920 - 1930 (Box-folder 284/1)
    - Blueprints, Greybull Division, circa 1920 - 1950 (Box-folder 284/2)
    - Blueprints, Kane Division, circa 1920 - 1930 (Box-folder 284/3)
    - Blueprints, Worland Division, circa 1920 - 1930 (Box-folder 284/4)
    - Blueprints, Worland Division, circa 1930 - 1940 (Box-folder 284/5)
    - Blueprints, Miscellaneous, circa 1920 - 1950 (Box-folder 284/6)
    - Blueprints, Miscellaneous, circa 1920 - 1940 (Box-folder 285/1)
    - Blueprints, Miscellaneous, circa 1910 - 1920 (Box-folder 285/2)
  - Clearwater Short Line Railway Company, 1890-1910; Series XXVIII; 15.5 linear feet